How far you think we've gone?
你觉得我们已经走了多远了
Fifty miles.
五十英里
Dude, we're almost to the woods.
就快要到树林了
put down!
快蹲下
What?
怎么了
A cop car!
有辆警车
There's no one in there.
车里一个人也没有
No way!
不会吧
Try this one.
试试踩这一个
Awesome.
太棒了
What if someone sees us?
要是有人看到我们了怎么办
We'll just tell them we're cops.
我们就跟他们说我们是警察
Good idea.
好主意
This is our cop car!
这是我们的警车
See how fast we can go.
看看我们能开多快
Sheriff, we just got a report of two kids driving a cruiser.
警长   刚有人报告说 有两个小孩在驾驶一辆警务巡逻车
Boys, I know you can hear me.
孩子们   我知道你们能听到我说话
You are in a whole lot of trouble.
你们有大麻烦了
What we're looking at is a felony offense.
我们会判你们重罪
Did you open up the trunk?
你们打开过后备箱吗
Are you a bad guy, sheriff?
警长   你是坏人吗
I know where to find you.
我知道去哪找你们
Are you okay?
你们没事吧
You don't   steal
你们不该 偷
a cop car!
警车